(Howard:)It's like going
with your grandpa.
(Howard:)Instead of eating popcorn,
(Howard:)he brings little pieces
of chicken in Tupperware
(Howard:)and a thermos full of soup.
(Leonard:)He's not that bad.
(Leonard:)Hey, Stuart, got any plans
Thursday night?
(Stuart:)My, uh... my doctor's worried
about my circulation,
(Stuart:)so I was thinking about
walking around the mall.
(Stuart:)Why?
(Sheldon:)Well...
Hey, you guys.
(Howard:)Oh, make sure
to wear sensible shoes.
(Howard:)Wil, want to go
to Star Wars Thursday?
(Wil:)Absolutely.
(Stuart:)Fine, take Wil.
See if he brings you
clam chowder.
(Penny:)Okay, okay, okay,
okay, okay.
Let's-let's... let's just
recap our options.
(Penny:)All right, we've got
harp thing, sheep thing...
(Bernadette:)Wild thang.
(Sheldon:)Which do you think
she'd prefer?
(Sheldon:)Because I checked the Sheep
and Wool Festival Web site,
(Sheldon:)and there's only
8,000 tickets left.
(Penny:)Sheldon, being physical with
Amy is a huge step for you.
(Bernadette:)Yeah, are you ready
for this?